(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T23:05:11.084819",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
BAU BAU!
Welcome to our 3rd anniversary and celebration of hololive!
And thanks to Haachama-senpai with the song, RED HEART!
Here we go!
RED HEART!
1, 2, 3, GO!
Hi, how are you?
Are you calling up my phone?
Baby, tell me what is wrong
Don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good
I am still looking for proof
Am I good enough for you?
Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me, are you coming on the ride?
We are going super high
Got to be who what I like
You and me, are you ready for the fight?
Alright
Stronger than I ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
...far away
You and me, we make that part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart
My red heart
Hi, over there, thank you for coming along
on this journey of my own, promise me you won't let go
Yes, this is me, I am falling, but I'm strong
'Cause you've got me in your arms, don't you ever let me go
I want you to come with me on the ride
This is going super high, I am falling from the sky
Got to be who you wanna be, that's right
Alright, alright, alright, alright!
Let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Haachama-chama!
I am still a girl
Figuring out what's true or false in this whole wide world
I'm your only girl
Tell me once more what's really going on with you
I'm looking for the right one on the road
The one that always take me back to you
This can be home, will you be my home?
Stronger than I ever been before
Stronger than I've ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
You and me, we make the part of me
You and me, we make that part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart
My, my red heart
Thank you for singing RED HEART
I give all of you guys my BIG RED HEART
from HAACHAMA
[On-screen: Thank you for singing RED HEART / I give all of you guys my BIG RED HEART / from HAACHAMA]
BAU BAU!
Thank you so much Ruffians for coming to
FUWAMOCO's 3rd Anniversary Live,
Thanks to hololive! BAU BAU!
FUWAMOCOの3周年記念ライブ
To FUWAMOCO's 3rd Anniversary Live,
「Thanks to hololive」に来てくれて
'Thanks to hololive,' for coming,
本当にありがとう！ BAU BAU!
thank you so much! BAU BAU!
Today, our entire concert is to share our love
and appreciation for holo, our senpai,
genmates, kouhai, and you! And of course, Ruffians!
そう！今日、3周年を記念して、
That's right! Today, to celebrate our 3rd anniversary,
今日はホロライブへの思いと感謝の気持ちを伝えるために、
today, to convey our feelings and gratitude to hololive,
思いっきり歌って踊ります！ Yeah!
we're going to sing and dance with all our might! Yeah!
And this stream is going to be packed
with all of our love for holo! Get ready, okay?
いっぱい込めてます！ Yeah!
It's packed with love! Yeah!
And, of course, you do want to know
our hashtag, right?
Yeah, very important!
Our hashtag for today is #FWMC3rd! Yeah!
見よう、見よう！ Do see ya! Yeah!
Let's check them out! Do see ya! Yeah!
Please take lots of screenshots, pasha-pasha,
Please take lots of screenshots, snap-snap,
and tweet about us on SNS, okay? BAU BAU!
うん！そう、ハッシュタグは #FWMC3rd で、
Yup! So with the hashtag #FWMC3rd,
スクリーンショットをたくさんSNSに投稿してくれるのを待ってるよ！
we'll be waiting for you to post lots of screenshots on SNS!
ポチッとして行くから！
We'll go like them!
Mococo, take a look and go, "Ooh, pochimococo!"
What're you doing? Ooh! Ha-ooh!
Okay! BAU BAU! Yeah, we're waiting! BAU BAU!
But our very first song that we performed
was Haachama-senpai's RED HEART!
RED HEART! Yeah! It's a very precious song of hers,
and, you know, it's because of Haachama-senpai
that actually FUWAMOCO, we found hololive!
そう！FUWAMOCOね、はあちゃま先輩のおかげで
That's right! Because of Haachama-senpai,
ホロライブに出会いましたから、とってもとっても大切な曲です！
FUWAMOCO found hololive, so it's a very, very precious song to us!
We love you so much, Haachama-senpai!
We're waiting to collab again, okay? Yeah, we love you!
We want bugs! Let's cook bugs together, okay?
そう、はあちゃま先輩大好きだよー！
Yeah, we love Haachama-senpai so much!
待ってるよー！
We're waiting!
わー！
Yay!
And look at this stage!
We designed today's stage with a very special hololive feel in mind, right?
You got that right!
そう、今回のステージはホロライブをテーマに作ってもらいました！
That's right, today's stage was created with a hololive theme!
We really hope that our love for hololive will reach you today!
Yeah! We'll be singing and dancing, of course, for some very special senpais, so please look forward to it!
Um, and...
Well, there might be a big announcement too!
そしてそして、重大発表もあるから、
And on top of that, we have a major announcement,
必ず最後まで見てください！
so make sure to watch until the very end!
Please watch to the very end, okay?
Stay tuned!
バウバウバウバウ！
Bau bau bau bau!
Happy anniversary!
Congratulations!
Yay! You made it!
Wouldn't miss it for the world!
Happy anniversary!
Adventのみんながお祝いに来てくれました！
Everyone from Advent came to celebrate with us!
Thank you!
Yeah, but you know, we just celebrated our third anniversary together a few weeks ago!
It was such a fun time, but now we're in our fourth year!
Fourth year?! What is happening?!
We're dead!
Well, before it's time to have an Advent funeral...
Shiori! You have anything to say? Happy third anniversary!
Thank you! It's been really nuts if you think about it,
because we've had the evolution of getting to know each other from the very first collab game
to now, three years later, we gift each other little silly gifts
like gnomes, a little cute plushier bookmark, and I just really appreciate being everyone's friend.
Yeah! Let's be friends for many more years to come!
Yes, so many years! All the years!
What about Nerissa?
Well, of course, it's FuwaMoco Day, so I'll mostly be talking about you,
but do keep in mind that I do feel this way about all of Advent, but...
You know, since we all got together,
it's just been so clear that all of us were meant to be friends, if you know what I mean.
Like, I truly can't imagine being in a gen with more hardworking and amazing people than you guys,
and every day I'm just so, so grateful to be able to have you guys here, as my friends and as my genmates. I'm so happy!
Aw, thank you! Love you too!
3周年おめでとうございます！
Happy 3rd anniversary!
Thank you! Hugging again!
Oh, are we fight touching right now?
Biboo! All right, let me hold your paws while I say this.
FuwaMoco, 3周... 3周年おめでとうございます！
FuwaMoco, ha... happy 3rd anniversary!
Yay!
You know, we've been through so much together as Advent,
and with you guys, you know, like you fed me bugs, you got me a microwave,
you made sure I didn't die, you held my hand as I crossed the street,
and I couldn't imagine starting this journey with anybody else other than you guys.
So I'm so happy we're here celebrating together!
Let's do more stuff with Advent together!
Advent!
It's really been an amazing three years!
Yeah! You know, but...
We love you!
Advent hug!
Let's continue strong together!
Yeah, even more fun!
But you know, our concert has only just started, right?
We get to sing together, the five of us, you know?
Well, FuwaMoco, we wanted to sing a song that means so much to us.
You know, without our senpais' hard work, we all wouldn't be here, you know?
When we all debuted, there was one senpai that were just about to celebrate their third anniversary too.
When we all debuted, there was one senpai that was just about to celebrate their third anniversary too.
So with all the love and respect in our hearts,
please listen to this very special version of hololive English -Myth-'s original song.
Here we go!
Reunion!
Sing out boldly again,
continuing this odyssey.
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
This is a precious song filled with memories sung by the very members who started hololive English!
We'll put all our love and respect into it, as Advent!
Ready? Set? Stream!
It's almost showtime, I would say,
It's not tomorrow, it's today!
But when times are ruff, is it really enough?
'Cause they're chasing me endlessly—why?
Take it easy, what have we learned?
When the cell doors open, it's our turn!
Yeah, we can do this, call the Adventrix!
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks.
Been on the run for so long that we really hit our stride!
Now look at all we've accomplished together side by side!
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai!
"Justice can't catch us!" "Moco-chan, behind you!"
"Hoeh?!"
Spanning new dimensions,
we can bring another mystery to light!
Planning our ascension, dancing in flight,
we ignite...
Through the stories we inspire, we can light another fire,
Advent's reaching even higher!
Through this world and beyond,
our distant dreams have brought us here.
A strong, unyielding bond, guiding us endlessly,
will bring us moments that we hold dear.
Time rushes on,
and though these winds may scatter us,
we'll keep this promise.
When the moment's finally right,
we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'll lend a helping paw, I can go the extra mile,
I'm gonna give my all, so let's protect your smile! Bau!
I'm rocking in again, now I'll never break my streak!
Gaming streams full of memes six or seven times a week! Yeah!
It's time for a pup talk, 'cause I know it's essential,
that even when we're in the doghouse, we've got endless potential!
It's time for paws-itive thoughts, so I keep on pondering donuts,
but now I'm getting warm and fuzzy from the love that you've shown us! BAU BAU!
Countless moments led us to this day:
Triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow—
we'll always find our way, come what may!
In every universe, we were always meant to meet.
I'll lead a boundless search. We will never know defeat!
My wings will guide your hands as the fateful days go by.
We will cut a path through a never-ending sky!
Shining bright together,
I can sense another wish is coming true.
We'll be friends fur-ever, loyal and true,
me and you!
Sing out again!
The clouded skies give way to clear;
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
Another story's starting right here...
We'll keep forging ahead
to make a saga all our own.
Whichever paths we tread,
steadily journeying,
we know we're never really alone.
If we believe,
wherever fate may find us,
our love will bind us.
Every epic chapter we write
will set us on the path to reunite!
Step and Go!!
昨日から止まったような時計
Like a clock that seems to have stopped since yesterday,
幼い頃をふと思い出した
I suddenly remembered my childhood.
あ〜
Ah~
もう心配しなくてもいいよ
You don't have to worry anymore,
あの優しい声が そばにあったから
because that gentle voice was right by my side.
不意に傷ついて 道に迷った日もあったけれど
Though there were days I got hurt and lost my way,
いつだって探してたのは 輝けるはずの better day
what I was always searching for was a better day that was sure to shine.
Everyday 解き放て 躊躇いがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, unleash that hesitation-prone emotion!
時代のせいにしたって つまらないよ
Blaming it on the times won't make things any fun.
Everyday 君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Everyday, stay true to yourself, even if there are days you come to a halt.
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, you're definitely going to be alright!
Step and go!
誰もが記憶の中にある 大切なあの笑顔
That precious smile everyone holds in their memories...
抱きしめてる
I'm holding onto it tight.
いつか君にまた会えたなら
If I ever get to meet you again,
素直にちゃんと 気持ち伝えたい
I want to honestly convey my feelings to you.
自分自身で引いた ボーダーラインなら さっと飛び越えて
If it's a borderline you drew yourself, jump right over it!
いつだって描いていこうよ 君らしい色で better day
Let's always paint a better day in your very own colors!
Everyday 閃いて 今動き出したエモーション
Everyday, let it spark—the emotions set in motion right now!
誰かのせいにしたって つまらないよ
Blaming it on someone else won't make things any fun.
Everyday らしくあれ やがてこの雨も上がって
Everyday, be true to yourself; soon, this rain will clear up, too.
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, you're definitely going to be alright!
Step and go!
挑んだ数だけ 涙は出るけど
Tears may fall as many times as we take on challenges,
やまない雨はないように
but just as no rain lasts forever,
君ならできるよ Step and go!
you can do it! Step and go!
Everyday 解き放て 躊躇いがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, unleash that hesitation-prone emotion!
時代のせいにしたって つまらないよ
Blaming it on the times won't make things any fun.
Everyday 君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Everyday, stay true to yourself, even if there are days you come to a halt.
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, you're definitely going to be alright!
Step and go!
FUWAMOCOの居場所である大好きなhololiveを作ってくれてありがとう♡
[Thank you for creating the hololive we love, a place where FUWAMOCO belongs♡]
でいり〜たいあり〜！
Daily Diary!
届けちゃおう！
Let's deliver it!
青春実況中！ 挑戦配信中！
Youth commentary live! Challenge streaming live!
ほらね 楽しいを発見！
See, I discovered something fun!
また新しい「好き」が見つかったよ
I found a new favorite thing again!
近所にできたカフェの ケーキ！
The cake from that newly opened cafe nearby!
なんかすごく美味しかったんだよ
It was just so delicious!
知らなかったゲームや
Games I never knew about,
聴いたことない歌
or songs I've never heard before...
ちょっと気になったら手を出してちゃおう
If you're even a little curious, dive right in!
ほ・ら・ま・た いっしょに遊ぼう！
Come on, let's play together again!
配信！ 10連ガチャ引いてみよう
Stream! Let's do a 10-pull gacha!
...引いてみよう (欲しい！)
...let's do a 10-pull gacha! (I want it!)
ホラーゲームやってみよう (絶叫！)
Let's play a horror game! (Screaming!)
あの曲歌ってみよう (感動！)
Let's sing that song! (So moving!)
全部がもう楽しいの！
Everything is just so fun!
窓の向こうの 笑顔に手を振っちゃおう！
Let's wave to the smiles beyond the window!
アニメ 四畳半中 (発見！)
In an anime within a tiny room, (Discovered!)
モブのキャラにも推せるポテンシャル
even a background character has fave potential!
締め切り追われた 漫画の名作 (名作！)
A masterpiece manga rushed by deadlines, (Classic!)
タイムラインについた新ネタ (爆笑！)
A new meme on the timeline! (Hilarious!)
当たんない天気予報もきっと
Even a weather forecast that's totally wrong
面白いことになるんだよ
is bound to turn into something fun!
(配信！) 聞いて聞いて 今日の朝 (なに？)
(Stream!) Listen, listen! This morning, (What?)
目覚まし鳴らなくて (え？)
my alarm didn't go off! (Huh?)
寝過ごしちゃったのは (どうして？) 昨晩の生放送！
The reason I overslept... (Why?) was last night's stream!
すごく楽しんで 寝つけなかったんだ (ああね！)
I had so much fun that I couldn't fall asleep! (I see!)
特別すごいことなんて そう起こらないリアル
In reality, amazing things don't happen often,
だけどそのエッセンス
but with those little moments
重なった世界
layering together,
夢に変えて 毎日がパラダイス
turning them into dreams makes every day paradise!
思い切り遊んで 笑っちゃおう
Let's play our hearts out and laugh together!
大成功！ (イエイ！)
Huge success! (Yay!)
全米を泣かす覚悟してきた
I came prepared to make all of America cry!
なにそれ？
What's that supposed to mean?
勝てる気もしないんだってー！
I don't feel like I can win at all!
諦めたら実況終了だよ？
If you give up, the stream is over, you know?
えー！まだ終わりたくない！
What?! I don't wanna end it yet!
どんな毎日も 楽しくなっちゃうんだ
Every single day turns into something fun!
出そう 一緒に出そう
Let's send it out, let's send it out together!
ほら あなたが待ってるの (イエイ！)
Look, you're waiting for us! (Yay!)
みんなで毎日を (配信！)
Every day with everyone, (Stream!)
出会えた嬉しいを (絶叫！)
the joy of meeting you, (Screaming!)
みんなと一緒に (土曜！)
together with everyone, (Saturday!)
気分はね もう最高潮！
our spirits are at an all-time high!
窓の向こうの 笑顔に手を振って
Waving our hands to the smiles beyond the window,
配信で届ける Daily Diary
we'll deliver our Daily Diary on stream!
青春実況中！ (色々)
Youth gaming live! (All sorts of things!)
挑戦配信中！ (試して)
Live challenge streaming! (Trying it out!)
青春実況中！ (いっぱい)
Youth gaming live! (Tons of things!)
挑戦配信中！ (遊ぼう)
Live challenge streaming! (Let's play!)
Daily Diary 届けよう！
Let's deliver our Daily Diary!
みんな大～すきっだよー！！
3年間分のDaily Diaryを
みんなと一緒につくりあげられたのは
最高の宝物♡♡
[We love you all so much!!
Being able to build 3 years of Daily Diary together with everyone is our greatest treasure ♡♡]
BAU BAU!
And that was...
Daily Diary!
Oeh!
We're really happy to perform it together with Mikochi-senpai, Korone-senpai, and Watame-senpai!
先輩たち！
Senpai-tachi!
BAU BAU! Ruffian!
But the reason why we chose Daily Diary was...
...is because...
Ruff!
Daily Diary is a really special song to us.
And we listened to it lots and lots before we debuted,
and we really, really desperately wanted to start creating our own Daily Diary
together with you, Ruffians!
With you! Ruff!
And also, listening to it over and over, we couldn't imagine what that might look like.
Ruff!
おい、そう！FUWAMOCOにとって、Daily Diaryはすごく大切な曲で、デビュー前にたくさん聴いてた曲です。
Yeah, that's right! For FUWAMOCO, Daily Diary is a very special song that we listened to a lot before our debut.
うん！
Yeah!
おい、その頃の気持ちはまだすごく覚えてて、早くデビューして、みんなとのDaily Diaryを作りたくて作りたくて！
I still remember those feelings so clearly—how we wanted to debut so quickly and build our Daily Diary with everyone!
作りたくて！
We wanted to so badly!
ねえ、しょうがなかったんですね！
We just couldn't help it!
でも、この3年間で、みんなと作ってきた思い出が、想像以上に素晴らしいDaily Diaryになってるよ！
But the memories we've made with everyone over these 3 years have become an even more wonderful Daily Diary than we ever imagined!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Thank you! おい！
Thank you! Yeah!
You know, the memories we made together have formed an even more wonderful Daily Diary that we could have ever imagined, you know?
You know, the memories we made together have formed an even more wonderful Daily Diary than we could have ever imagined, you know?
Thank you all for everything!
Thank you! Ruff!
BAU!
Ah? Ah?
You know, I think we still have a lot more coming up, including...
Ooh! Including what, Moco-chan?
A super-duper big announcement!
Announcement! Yeah! Ruff!
It's really important, okay?
重大告知まであと少しだよ！
Not much longer until the major announcement!
あと少し！
Just a little bit!
Ruff! 忘れてないよね？
Ruff! You haven't forgotten, right?
やあやあやあ！
No, no, no!
You can't miss it, okay?
So make sure you stay with us until the very end!
Very end! Ruff!
But, we still have some very special songs we'd like to sing for you!
Sing for you! Yeah!
Ruff!
I'm a little nervous, Moco-chan!
I'm nervous too!
Well, let's get ready then, Moco-chan.
Okay.
Let's get going!
Okay!
BAU BAU! Here we go! BAU BAU!
君のヒロインは誰？
Who is your heroine?
覚えてる優しさに
I still remember your kindness,
君の言葉にキュンとして
and my heart fluttered at your words.
上手に言えない
Unable to find the right words,
代わりに笑いかけてみたの
I gave you a smile instead.
目が合った気がした それだけで
Just feeling like our eyes met
鼓動跳ねた お願い
made my heart leap. Please,
勘違いじゃありませんように
please don't let it be a misunderstanding.
そっと心の中で 熱視線送った
Quietly in my heart, I sent you a passionate gaze,
振り向いてって 願っちゃってた
wishing that you would turn around.
ヒロインオーディション エントリーしたら私
If I entered the heroine audition,
ねぇ 選んでくれるかな
hey, would you choose me?
真面目な性格
Your earnest personality...
「おはよう」だけで伝わるよ
I can tell just from your "Good morning."
何気ないつぶやき
At your casual murmurs,
もしかしてと期待してる
I secretly get my hopes up.
眩しい素敵な人ばかりで
Surrounded by such dazzling, wonderful people,
自信もなくて
I have no confidence at all,
それでも本音では
but deep down in my heart...
365日 もっと近づきたい
All 365 days, I want to get closer to you.
私なりのペースになるけど
Even if it's at my own slow pace,
ヒロインオーディション 勇気を出したら君は
in the heroine audition, if I muster up my courage,
ねぇ 応えてくれるかな
hey, will you answer me?
出会った一瞬ってかなりすごいミラクル
The moment we met was truly an amazing miracle.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is a red thread of fate.
ギュッと手繰り寄せて 運命にしよう
Let's reel it tight and turn it into destiny.
信じて まっすぐ せーので言葉にして
Believing straight ahead, let's say it out loud on three!
君のヒロインは誰？
Who is your heroine?
ぎゅっと君の心を 動かしてみせるよ
I'll definitely move your heart.
まだまだ全然足りないけど
Even though I'm still not nearly enough,
ヒロインオーディション 選んでそして私を
in the heroine audition, choose me, and then...
いつかぎゅっとしてほしい
I want you to hold me tight someday.
ありがとう ずっと大好きだよ
Thank you, I will love you forever!
もういいじゃん むきになっちゃって格好つけて
Enough already! Getting so defensive and trying to act cool,
格好良くない そういうの嫌になってんだ ほっといてよ 知りたくない
you're not cool at all. I'm sick of that, leave me alone, I don't wanna know.
もういいじゃん やけになってんの 嫉妬したりじっとできない
Enough already! You're so desperate, getting jealous and unable to sit still.
聞こえないよう耳塞いだって 言ってくるじゃん しんどいな
Even if I cover my ears so I can't hear, you still say it. How exhausting.
僕は誰も覗かないよ だから僕のことそっとしといて
I won't pry into anyone, so just leave me alone.
うざいだけの馬鹿にハイハイハイ ウケる「またのお越し待ってるね」だとか
Giving a "Yeah, yeah, yeah" to the annoying idiot. Hilarious, saying stuff like "Looking forward to your next visit!"
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
In reality, you're just a terrified coward who does nothing but bark.
痛くて居たいってハイハイハイ いつも意識のフリばっかなの
Crying "It hurts, but I want to stay," yeah, yeah, yeah, always just pretending to be conscious.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないでってって
I laugh with my barrier up: "Don't come any closer than that."
怖いくせに
Even though you're scared.
ばかばっか ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, nothing but idiots.
ばかばっか 嫌 ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, no! Nothing but idiots.
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの ほっといてよ ほっとできない
Enough already! Are you still mad? "Leave me alone." I can't leave you alone.
見ないように目を逸らしたって ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
Even if I avert my eyes so I don't look, you follow right behind me as expected.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん 見失ってるなら探せばいいじゃん いやいやいやいやいや それでよくない？
If you fall, just get back up! If you lost it, just search for it! No no no no no, wouldn't that be fine?
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん 嫌になったらやめればいいじゃん いやいやいやいやいや それでよくない？
If you make a mistake, just fix it! If you get sick of it, just quit! No no no no no, wouldn't that be fine?
僕は誰も覗か…
I won't pry into anyo—
...わないよ だから僕のことそっとしといて
...no match for you, so just leave me alone.
嫌なこと全部「大丈夫」だと言えたらいいのにな
I wish I could just say "it's okay" to everything I hate.
思えたらいいのにな
I wish I could feel that way.
機嫌を伺えたら大正解 いつも僕はそんなロールなの
Reading the room is the right move—that's always my role.
また言いたいことを殺したから もう忘れてくれ
I've killed what I wanted to say again, so just forget it.
うわっはっはー
Uwahaha!
ふざけただけの馬鹿にハイハイハイ (受けるー)
Saying "Yeah, yeah, yeah" to fools just messing around (Hilarious!)
またのお越し待ってる面汚しとか
Like a disgrace waiting for them to visit again,
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
I was really just a terrified coward, all bark and no bite.
痛いくせに咲いてハイハイハイ いつも平気なフリばっかなの
In pain yet putting on a show, "Yeah, yeah, yeah," always just pretending I'm fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで
I smile while keeping my guard up—don't come any closer.
どうか
Please.
本当馬鹿ばっか いい加減ばっか とんだバグばっか だせえなって
Seriously, just idiots everywhere, so irresponsible, nothing but ridiculous bugs—how lame.
そんな言葉吐く僕もやっぱ どうしようもない 黙ってようか
Spitting such words, I'm hopeless too—maybe I should just stay quiet.
正解の答えなら「ないない」死ねるって 僕の口ばっかだね
If there's a correct answer, it's "none"—saying "I could die," it's all talk from me.
今日も壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないでってって
Today again, I smile with my walls up, saying "Don't come any closer!"
怖いじゃん 馬鹿ばっか ほら 馬鹿ばっか
Isn't it scary? Nothing but fools! Look, nothing but fools!
[Duet with Lui-senpai♡ / いつかルイせんぱいみたいにCOOLになりたい〜!! / がんばるるね BAU BAU! Thank You♡]
[Duet with Lui-senpai♡ / I want to be cool like Lui-senpai someday~!! / I'll do my best! BAU BAU! Thank you♡]
3, 2, 1
Chu Chu Chu Chu...
何気ない声が そわそわ ちょっとお粗末がいいな まだまだだけど
A casual voice makes me restless; a little clumsy is nice, though there's still a long way to go.
いつからかそれが 眩しくなる
Sometime along the way, that became dazzling.
Ah-ah-ah-ah
気づいてんじゃない？ きっと甘い そんな言葉で Yeah
Aren't you noticing? Surely with such sweet words, yeah.
Ah-ah-ah-ah
もっとハマっちゃって ねえ 弓を射っちゃって
Fall even deeper for me—come on, shoot your bow!
空から今 落ちてく 飛んでく 何処か 欲しく虜にして 渦巻く恋熱 解して
Falling from the sky now, flying off somewhere, making you mine and captive, unraveling this swirling fever of love.
もう君は最低だ 叶わないな
You're truly the worst—I just can't compete.
君のキューピッドです また夢中 Chu
I'm your Cupid, crazy about you again, chu!
きっと夢に出てくる Chu Chu Chu Chu...
I'm sure I'll appear in your dreams, chu chu chu chu...
痛いのよ今も
It still hurts, even now.
きゅーきゅーです また胸ギュッとなんだかデリケート
It's squeezing tight—my heart clenches again, somehow so delicate.
Chu Chu Chu Chu...
ぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me tight.
どうして？ Rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta
Why? Rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta, rat-ta-ta
君はまだ知らない事情 私も見えてないでしょう
Circumstances you don't yet know—I probably can't see them either, right?
泣いちゃった 泣いちゃった 泣いちゃった 泣いちゃった
I ended up crying, crying, crying, crying.
あの子には見せちゃう微笑 想うだけで熱上昇
Showing that smile only to them, fever rising just from thinking about it.
会いたい衝動 その眼差し Ah
The urge to see you, that gaze, ah.
探し続けた 宝石みたい
Like a gem I've searched for all along.
でも まだまだ 気づくことピンチだ 浮かせる足も愛して 凍てつく鈍色愛して
But still, realizing it spells trouble—love even my restless feet, love even the frozen dull gray.
ああ もうあたし最低だ 辞めれないから
Ah, I'm truly the worst, because I can't stop.
君のキューピッドです また夢中 Chu
I'm your Cupid, crazy about you again, chu!
もっと欲しくなってく Chu Chu Chu Chu...
Wanting you even more, chu chu chu chu...
期待をしちゃうよ
I'm getting my hopes up.
Give you love 感情流入 ずっと気持ち溢れる
Give you love, pouring emotions in, feelings overflowing endlessly.
Chu Chu Chu Chu... ぎゅっと抱きしめて
Chu Chu Chu Chu... Hold me tight.
ぎゅっと抱きしめて ぎゅっと...
Hold me tight, tight...
ああ もう隠せないけど 止まらない鼓動
Ah, I can no longer hide it, this unstoppable heartbeat.
夢から覚めて 気づいて今
Wake up from the dream and realize it now.
[かなたせんぱい♡ / 「きゅーぴっど。」を歌ったよー!! / ずーっと忘れないよー!! / we LOVE you♡]
[Kanata-senpai♡ / We sang "Cupid."!! / We'll never forget it!! / We LOVE you♡]
We'd run right through
those nights, I'll never find my way back to
...to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning
never laugh less
we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died
I'll fly, no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say, hey, thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless
it was stinging
running roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died
What was the root of it all? Huh, I couldn't say
Used to jump and then fall, rugged and cliché
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
No use in trying to find friends, 'cause in the end nobody sticks around
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
That you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space
Cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams
Just what the hell was so funny?
Bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights
Amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right
We mixed the ennui and troubles, rhyming our discontent
And though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent
Convinced that this could mean another end exists between real and pretend
A twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend, and
Disappearing into the mist of never happened, is the me that I can never befriend
I let it go
Fade in, fade out
this crazy dream
Without a direction,
floating aimlessly
There's nothing left back there for me
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring
We'd run right through
those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning
never laugh less
we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died
But was there ever a soul inside?
Chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises
Left a trail behind, defined it, wasted time of our lives
Silent singer, overworked and underpaid
Thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
Yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid
Saw the nothing wrong in writing songs behind the lonely shade
Is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
When the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played?
Does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed
And your friends grew tired of fantasy, you're wishing they had stayed?
You don't get to say I miss you, you watched your heroes fade
Into the rear view mirror of the villain you portrayed
into the rearview mirror of the villain you portrayed.
Stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed
You don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made
These the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade
Recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this
What is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out
this hazy dream
Without a direction,
roaming aimlessly
There's nothing left back there for me
Pretend it's the end of a made-up story
I'll fly, no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say, hey, thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless
it was stinging
driving roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died
I'll say goodbye to the soul inside
And yet somehow, there was romance
in our self-hate, we've got no chance
in this light maze, but let's hold hands
through the night haze, we'll run so fast
'til the school chime, 'til the train runs
We know it's time, we're the sane ones
Waking up now, to the real life
Let me daydream, 'til the next night
I'll keep waiting
I'll keep waiting for you
Waking up now, to my real life
let me daydream, 'til the next flight
Drowning so long, I got older
now the crowd's gone, is it over?
Is it over?
一途ってトレンド♡
[New Song: Devotion is Trending♡]
さて 教えましょう
Now then, let me teach you
粋な恋のルールを
the stylish rules of love.
いい？ 女の子は
Got it? The only girl
私だけなの
in your eyes is me.
申し訳ございません
I'm terribly sorry,
貴方の世界には
but in your world,
他1人居場所なんてあるはずないの
there couldn't possibly be room for anyone else.
誰もが
To a level that
羨む
everyone envies,
レベルで愛してよ
love me just like that.
思わず
A love that makes you
真似してみたくなるような
unconsciously want to imitate it,
恋しよ
let's fall in love!
ねえ 流行っちゃってる
Hey, it's totally trending,
Lovey-dovey
一途ってトレンド
Being devoted is the trend!
よそ見なんてね
Looking elsewhere,
Darling darling
時代遅れなの
is so out of style!
Only One同士よ 好き好き
We're each other's only one, love ya, love ya!
いつだって私でしょ
It's always me, right?
貴方はほら
Come on, you should
最先端でいてよ
stay on the cutting edge!
じゃあ 教えてよ
Then tell me,
貴方の頭の中
what's inside your head?
照れくさそうな目も
Even those shy eyes of yours
私のモノよ
belong completely to me.
少しの秘密も
Even the smallest secret
2人にあり得ないわ
is impossible between the two of us!
全てを預けて
Entrust everything to me,
隠し事なんて無しだよ
no secrets allowed!
ねえ 気付いちゃってる
Hey, you've realized it,
Lovey-dovey
素直ってトレンド
Being honest is the trend!
秘密なんてね
Keeping secrets,
Darling darling
的外れなのよ
is totally missing the mark!
正直同士よ 好き好き
We're both honest with each other, love ya, love ya!
永遠に結びましょう
Let's tie our bond forever!
貴方はほら
Come on, you should
最前線でいてよ
stay on the front line!
どんなときも胸を震わせてね
Make my heart flutter at all times, okay?
離れていても
Even when we're apart...
ほら 貴方って そう 貴方って
Look, you... yes, you...
こんなに素敵なの
are just so wonderful!
この世のこの世の終わりまで
Until the very end of the world,
何から何まで繋ぎましょう
let's connect every single thing!
私の私の宝物
You're my, my treasure...
そうでしょ？ そうでしょ？
Isn't that right? Isn't that right?
恋しよ
Let's fall in love!
ねえ 流行っちゃってる
Hey, it's totally trending,
Lovey-dovey
一途ってトレンド
Being devoted is the trend!
よそ見なんてね
Looking elsewhere,
Darling darling
時代遅れなの
is so out of style!
Only One同士よ 好き好き
We're each other's only one, love ya, love ya!
いつだって私でしょ
It's always me, right?
貴方はほら
Come on, you should
最先端でいてよ
stay on the cutting edge!
私だけでいてよ
Keep your eyes only on me!
お願い お願い
Please, please!
私だけよ
Only me!
お願い お願い
Please, please!
私だけでいてよ
Keep your eyes only on me!
Ruffians!
That was our brand new original song, "Ichizutte Trend"!
やったー！そう、僕たちのオリジナル曲、「一途ってトレンド」でしたー！
Yay! Yes, that was our original song, "Ichizutte Trend"!
どうだったかな？
How did you like it?
新曲だよ！
It's a new song!
It was written and composed by the amazing Kiyoshi Ryujin-san!
So you know, he's written so many songs for idols and seiyuu that we really, really love!
We're so, so honored! Thank you!
そう、作詞作曲は清竜人さんでしたー！
Yes, the lyrics and music were composed by Kiyoshi Ryujin-san!
清さんにオリ曲を書いていただけて光栄です！
It's such an honor to have Kiyoshi-san write an original song for us!
夢！
It's a dream!
And it's our loveliest, dopest song yet!
So you know, we hope you like it lots and lots!
And it will be released on digital streaming at midnight JST!
Right after this! Right after!
It would make us really happy if you could listen to it lots and lots and lots and lots!
この配信の後、0時からデジタルリリースされますので、
It will be released digitally starting from midnight right after this stream,
いっぱい聴いてくれたら嬉しいな！
so we'd be so happy if you listen to it a lot!
Please! 「一途ってトレンド」！
Please! "Ichizutte Trend"!
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
Was that our big announcement?
Ah, does it think so? No, no, no!
Ah, do you think so? No, no, no!
Well, it's a big part, it's an original song! Yeah!
Yeah! But more! 今のオリ曲...
Yeah! But there's more! The original song just now...
重大告知だったっけ？
...Was it a major announcement?
What do you think, Ruffians?
No, no, no, no!
I was excited to have a new original song by us...
Not quite yet! We still have something, huh?
Did you want to take a look at it?
Do you want to know what the big announcement is?
Yeah, Ruffians! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay!
じゃあ、モコちゃん、言っちゃおうか！
Well then, Moco-chan, shall we tell them?
Okay! Here we go!
どうぞー！
Here you go!
一生Showtime 一緒に居たい
A lifetime showtime, I want to be with you forever.
All Lifetime Showtime, Anytime BAU BAU
一生涯 sing with you
A whole lifetime to sing with you...
めくるめくランデヴー 迷宮で待ってる
A dazzling rendezvous, waiting in the labyrinth...
背中に君を感じてたいの
I want to feel your back behind me.
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwa fuwa, moko moko!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
The Hellhound Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕 “BAU”DOLです
Born into this world, we are BAU-DOLs!
BAU BAU!
私たちFUWAMOCOの1stアルバムの発売が決定しましたー！
The release of FUWAMOCO's 1st album has been decided!
アルバムタイトルは「FUWAMOCO à la mode 〜いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのッ〜」
The album title is "FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~"!
ジャケットイラストは、イラストレーターの渡辺明夫先生！
The jacket illustration is by illustrator Akio Watanabe-sensei!
FUWAMOCOの憧れの方に描いてもらえることになって、本当に嬉しいです！
We're so happy that someone we admire is drawing for FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
現在製作中のイラストを特別に見せちゃいまーす！
We'll give you a special sneak peek at the illustration in progress!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
今回のアルバムは2枚組で作りましたー！
We made this album as a 2-disc set!
ディスク1の収録楽曲はなんと11曲！新曲もたくさんです！
Disc 1 features an amazing 11 tracks! With lots of brand new songs!
ディスク2は、ADVENTのオリジナル曲のFUWAMOCO歌唱バージョンと、アルバムについて語っているアフターパーティーです！
Disc 2 has FUWAMOCO's vocal versions of ADVENT original songs, plus an after-party discussing the album!
詳細はまだ内緒だから、続報を待っててねー！
The details are still a secret, so look forward to further updates!
さらにさらに！アルバムにはCD以外のものもたくさん詰め込みましたー！
And what's more, we packed plenty of goods beyond just the CDs into the album!
キラキラスペシャルシート、アクスタ、ホロカ、アナザージャケット、
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, holocard, alternate jacket,
そして2人で心を込めてRuffiansに向けて書いたお手紙！
and a heartfelt letter written by both of us just for Ruffians!
そしてそして！2人で頑張って買ってくれたみなさん全員に直筆サインを書くよー！
And what's more! The two of us will work hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
おー！
Ooh!
私たちの1stアルバム、たくさんの人が聴いてくれたら嬉しいなー！
We'd be so happy if lots of people listen to our 1st album!
We have huge news! Our very first album is finally happening!
The title is "FUWAMOCO à la mode ~いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのッ~"!
The title is "FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~"!
The cover illustration is by Akio Watanabe-sensei!
An illustrator we've always looked up to! We're so happy he agreed to draw for us!
BAU BAU!
And we want to show you something special right now! The illustration is still in progress!
Ta-da!
This album is a two-disc set!
Disc 1 has 11 songs, and so many brand-new ones!
Disc 2 is FUWAMOCO's own vocal version of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking all about the album!
But you know what, we can't spill any more details yet, so stay tuned!
And that's not all!
The album is packed with more than just the CD!
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, Holo card, an alternate jacket,
and a letter that the two of us wrote from our hearts, just for you!
And you know what, the two of us are working hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
We'd be so happy if lots of Ruffians get to listen to our first album!
BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! We're so happy!
It's finally here! It's happening! An album! An album!
ずっと夢見てたFUWAMOCOのアルバムですよー！
It's the FUWAMOCO album we've always dreamed of!
Look, CD! CD!
Look, Moco-chan has it! I hold it so gently! Album!
Yeah! This is it! This is the album we always dreamed of, Ruffians!
Yeah! Ooh!
This means, Moco-chan... You can hold it in your paws, too!
In your paws, Ruffians! Holding it!
Yeah! Thank you, Ruffians! Thank you for always supporting us! We're so happy!
いっぱい応援してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for giving us so much support!
ありがとう！本当にみんなのおかげだよー！
Thank you! It's really all thanks to everyone!
It's thanks to you Ruffians that we can do all of these amazing things! 本当に...
It's thanks to you Ruffians that we can do all of these amazing things! Really...
本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much!
But... but...
To repeat the important points, okay?
Pre-orders start very soon!
9:00 PM JST or 5:00 AM PDT!
Yeah, right after this, okay? Right away!
販売は今日21時、そう、このあとすぐ
Sales start today at 21:00, that's right, right after this,
から受注開始します！
pre-orders will open!
Are you ready? -Ready! -Yeah!
And, like we mentioned, every single CD will be signed by us!
That's right, by hand! Yeah, with these paws!
And it's gonna be signed with all our love! -All our heart!
CD全部、全部この2人から直筆サインがありますよ！
Every single CD will have an authentic handwritten signature from the two of us!
書きますよ！
We'll be signing them!
心を込めて大事に作ってるアルバムなので、みんなの手元に届いてほしいです！
It's an album made with lots of love and care, so we hope it reaches everyone's hands!
Please take one, please!
This album really means so much to us, so it would mean everything...
...if you could get a copy and add it to your collection...
...and listen to all of our precious songs that we put all our hearts into!
All the moments, all the time, okay?
You know, this is the day! The day we've been dreaming of this entire three years!
Thank you!
And Ruffians, you know it's not done here yet!
We'll continue to work really hard on it so it'll be everything that you dream of too, Ruffians, okay?
Thank you, Ruffians!
You're excited?
Yeah, please get it right after this, okay?
And don't forget! -忘れないでね！
And don't forget! -Don't forget!
All right, well, Ruffians, with that, we'd like to continue to sing two final songs for you today!
And one of the songs is a senpai song who we really admire as an idol!
And one of the songs is by a senpai whom we really admire as an idol!
次の曲はアイドルとしてとっても尊敬していた先輩の曲です！
The next song is by a senpai we deeply respected as an idol!
Ruffians, we hope our feelings reach you!
Please listen to: #Aqua Iro Palette!
何をしても不器用で 何かとミスしてばっか
No matter what I do, I'm clumsy and constantly messing up,
ダメダメな私だって できる事があるの
but even someone useless like me has things I can do!
凹んで悲しくたって 笑顔にしてあげるんだ
Even if you're feeling down and sad, I'll make you smile!
ここにいるから早く 私を見つけてね
I'm right here, so please find me soon!
Love you, love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah, I love you so much
Love you, love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
あぁ 愛して もっと
Ah, love me more!
いつでも隣にいるし いつでも一緒に笑える
I'll always be by your side, and we can always laugh together.
私をたくさん知って たくさん好きって言って
Get to know lots about me, and tell me that you love me a lot!
ワガママで朝も苦手 ドジだしダメダメだけど
I'm selfish and hate mornings, clumsy and no good, but...
それでも私の事を 見ててね
...even so, please keep watching me!
描く夢の未来へ続く
Leading towards the future of our painted dreams...
道をキミと歩けますように
...may I walk this road together with you.
ねぇ もっと好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっか
My head is full of nothing but you!
ってゆーかそっぽなんて向いてないで
I mean, don't look away from me!
あぁもうヤキモチしちゃうわ あぁ
Ah, jeez! You're making me jealous, ah!
ずっとずっと好きがいいの
I want you to love me forever and ever!
心の奥もトキメイちゃうくらいに
So much that my heart flutters deep inside,
こっち向いててよね ダーリン
keep looking this way, darling!
あぁもう離さないから 絶対に
Ah, I won't ever let you go, definitely!
Love you, love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
あぁ 愛して もっと
Ah, love me more!
キミがいるから私 いつでも頑張れるんだ
Because you're here, I can always give it my all!
落ち込んで悲しくたって キミがいるから
Even when I'm feeling down and sad, because you're here...
君がいるから歩いてこれた
Because you were here, I was able to walk this far.
次はいなくちゃ前も見えない
If you're not there next time, I won't even be able to look ahead.
嫌なこととか 辛いこととか 明日あって
Even if there are bad things or tough times tomorrow,
君の力でここまで笑ってこれたんだ
your strength is what let me come this far smiling.
今度こそは私がグッと引っ張って連れて行くんだ
This time, I'll be the one to pull you forward and lead the way.
君がいるから私がいるの
Because you are here, I am here.
こんな私を愛してくれて
Thank you for loving someone like me.
ねえもっと ねえもっと まだもっと 受け止めてよね
Hey, more and more, accept even more of me, okay?
ねえ ねえ、いい？
Hey... Is that okay?
さあ声を上げて
Come on, raise your voices!
ねえもっと ねえもっと 好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, more and more, I want you to love me even more!
いつでもそう私ばっか見てて そっぽなんて向かせないわ
Always look only at me, I won't let you look away!
ねえほら夢中にしちゃうわ ああ
Hey, look, I'll make you fall head over heels, ah!
ずっとずっと好きがいいの 心も体も染まっちゃうくらいに
I want you to love me forever and ever, so much that your heart and body are dyed in my color.
こっち向いててよね ダーリン 目を離さないから
Keep looking this way, darling, I won't take my eyes off you.
絶対に 絶対ね 絶対よ 約束だよ ああ
Absolutely, definitely, promise me, it's a promise, ah!
I love you, oh oh oh oh, love you, love you, oh oh oh oh
I love you so much, love you, love you, oh oh oh oh, I love you, oh oh oh oh, love you, love you, oh oh oh oh
愛しちゃうもっと
Love me even more!
This next song is our last song!
Let's continue to love hololive more and more!
いつの間にか見つけてた遠い夢
A distant dream I found before I knew it,
一人じゃ見えなかった景色
a scenery I couldn't have seen on my own.
波打つ風の音と 加速していく想いに
To the sound of the surging wind and feelings speeding up,
戸惑いを覚えた
I felt bewildered.
ずっと追いかけた
The ideal figure
理想の姿は まだ届かなくて遠いけど
I've always chased is still far away and out of reach, but...
きっとこの瞬間を かけがえないみんなで
surely in this moment, together with everyone irreplaceable,
共にいくよ 手をつないで
we'll go together, holding hands!
3, 2, 1!
輝き宿して
Dwelling with radiance,
夢の場所へ!
to the place of our dreams!
駆け抜けていく 僕たちの青春の光は
The light of our youth running through
誰にも止められないよ!
cannot be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う分だけ (優しく) 零れる涙さえ (今)
As much as we laugh together (gently), even spilling tears (now),
ほら輝かせ 明日へ運ぶから
look, we'll make them shine and carry them to tomorrow.
君の隣へ
To your side,
僕たちは世界を超えていく
we will transcend worlds,
迎えに行くよ
and come to greet you!
まだ見えない明日も きらめきに変えて
Turning even the unseen tomorrow into sparkle,
きっと僕たちが未来へと 連れて行くから!
we will surely lead you to the future!
背伸びしては手を伸ばす 憧れの
Reaching out on tiptoe, to that longing...
行き先示す 星になろう
Let's become stars that show the destination!
つまずくその度に 手を差し伸べ合えたら
Every time we stumble, if we can reach out our hands to each other,
すぐに届くはずさ
we're sure to reach it right away!
そっと踏み出した 小さな勇気が
The small courage that gently took a step forward,
もう消えないように 繋げよう
let's connect it so it will never fade!
不安も愛しさも 大切に抱きしめて
Embracing both our anxiety and affection dearly,
共にいくよ
we'll go together!
目を合わせて 日常は晴れ渡る希望へ
Locking eyes, daily life turns toward clear, sweeping hope,
飛び出せるよ!
we can leap right in!
突き抜けていく 僕たちの透き通る決意は
Breaking through, our crystal-clear determination
まだまだ止められないよ!
still can't be stopped!
ありきたりな今日こそ ときめきに変えて
Turning this ordinary today into excitement,
もっと僕たちがいつまでも 背中押すから!
we'll keep giving you a push forward forever!
Ruffians!
We have something we want to share with you!
It's now been three years since we made our debut here in hololive!
There's been so many precious memories made, laughs together,
and even some tears during rough times, too.
There's been lots of challenges, but it's all been worth it!
The energy and dreams we jumped with three years ago have been coming true one by one.
And now, our dream of our own first full vocal album is coming true, too!
And we're so excited and thankful!
We want to continue on this journey no matter what comes our way.
As long as we're together, we know that we can do the impossible!
Thank you for being our precious Ruffians here by our side.
We'll continue to protect your smiles forever and ever!
Bau bau!
二人で描いてた キャンバス
The canvas that the two of us painted on,
いつからかこんなに大きくなって
has somehow grown so big over time.
また少しずつ 芽生える「大好き」を紡ぎ
Once again, little by little, spinning the sprouting "love,"
どこまでも高く
reaching endlessly higher,
明日色の空へ
toward tomorrow's colored sky!
駆け抜けていく 僕たちの
Racing through, our...
青春の光は 誰にも止められないよ
The light of our youth can't be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う胸に（優しく） こぼれる涙さえ
In our laughing hearts, (gently) even spilling tears...
ほら 輝かせ 明日へ運ぶから
See, we'll make them shine and carry them into tomorrow,
君の隣へ
right to your side!
僕たちは 世界を超えていく
We're crossing beyond the world
迎えに行くよ
to come and reach you!
まだ見えない明日も きらめきに変えて
Turning even the unseen tomorrow into sparkle,
きっと僕たちが 未来へと
surely we will, into the future—
果てのない未来へと
Into an endless future,
連れて行くから
we'll take you there!
Thank you for 3 Years!!
It's because of you that we can shine so bright! The diary of memories we've made together these 3 years means everything to us! - Fuwawa
We're looking forward to even greater adventures in the future together! We'll become even brighter, stronger dogs so we can protect your smile furr-ever and ever! - Mococo